talkbeer.com 2016-11-20

# Privacy | TalkBeer - Craft beer news, info, discussion and trading.

**TalkBeer - Craft beer news, info, discussion and trading.**

[Home](http://www.talkbeer.com/) Help >

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy sets out how TalkBeer uses and protects any information that you provide, while using TalkBeer products and services. This includes, but is not limited to, TalkBeer.com and any associated websites and sub-domains.

TalkBeer is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any information provided by you to TalkBeer, by which you can be identified, will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

TalkBeer may change this policy as and when necessary. It is your responsibility to check this privacy policy periodically to ensure you agree with any changes.

**What information we collect**

When using any products and services provided by TalkBeer, we may require some or all of the following information:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Telephone number
  * Email address
  * Information related to any financial transactions which may be carried out

Additionally, while using the TalkBeer.com website, any associated websites and sub-domains, some or all of the following information may be collected:

  * IP address
  * Geographical location
  * Browser type and version
  * Operating system
  * Referral source
  * Length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity

**What we do with the information we collect**

The information you provide to TalkBeer is required for, but not limited to, the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping and analysis
  * Access to the TalkBeer.com website, associated websites and sub-domains
  * Account management
  * Purchase confirmation and account reset
  * Confirmation of email address
  * Sending relevant communications
  * Security

**How we use cookies and IP addresses**

TalkBeer.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, use small text files, called cookies, to store information in your web browser. The information stored may include preferences, session identification, HTTP information, and IP address. Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to have TalkBeer cookies stored on your device and used for the purposes outlined here and throughout the Terms of Service.

You can set your browser to not receive cookies, but this may limit your ability to use TalkBeer.com and any associated websites and sub-domains.

IP addresses of computers used to visit TalkBeer.com and any associated websites and sub-domains are stored in our database. This includes when first registering for an account, managing your account details, writing a private or public message or performing any other transaction which results in data being transferred to or from your computer and the website in question.

Your IP address is not visible to the public at any time.

**Links to other websites**

TalkBeer.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with TalkBeer.

TalkBeer has no control over any external websites therefore clicking any link which results in you visiting an external website will result in this privacy policy no longer applying and TalkBeer cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites.

**Controlling your personal information**

When using the TalkBeer.com forum, you may choose to limit public viewing of applicable personal information through the settings located in the Privacy section of your account.

TalkBeer will not sell, distribute or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you information pertaining to TalkBeer or your account.

If you discover any of the information TalkBeer holds for you is incorrect or incomplete, that you are unable to change yourself, please contact us as soon as possible so the necessary changes can be made.

**TalkBeer - Craft beer news, info, discussion and trading.**

[Home](http://www.talkbeer.com/) Help >
